fashionuniverse.net 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Pakistani Drama Celebrities

### **At www.fashionuniverse.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.fashionuniverse.net and how it is used.  **

## Who we are

www.fashionuniverse.net is a website about fashion and Celebrities mostly from Pakistan, cover fashion shows,fashion parties,new collection of brands and pakistani celebrities news.

you can contact at admin@fashionuniverse.net

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### Facebook Comments (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook, Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

## Cookies

www.fashionuniverse.net does not use cookies.

**We use Advertising Services listed below** that may use Cookies to identify Users or use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the User’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Application. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.  
In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

### Facebook Audience Network 

Facebook Audience Network is an advertising service provided by Facebook, Inc. In order to understand Facebook’s use of Data, consult  **[Facebook’s data policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).**

This Application may use identifiers for mobile devices (including Android Advertising ID or Advertising Identifier for iOS, respectively) and technologies similar to cookies to run the Facebook Audience Network service. One of the ways Audience Network shows ads is by using the User’s ad preferences. The User can control this in the [Facebook ad settings](https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings).

Users may opt-out of certain Audience Network targeting through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or by following the instructions in other Audience Network related sections of this privacy policy, if available.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example) and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads).

for more details and information [https://facebook.com/help/568137493302217?_rdc=1&_rdr](https://web.facebook.com/help/568137493302217?_rdc=1&_rdr)

### Google Adsense

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.fashionuniverse.net does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
. **::** Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.fashionuniverse.net.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.fashionuniverse.net and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

www.fashionuniverse.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should Go to the provided links with each service we use to opt out or for more information www.fashionuniverse.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

**For for Information on how Google use your data[read this  ](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/)**

**If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  **

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

We Do not Store and Share any Data but the services we use may share your data for which we mention the names and links below for more information and how you can opt out.

**Facebook Audience Network   [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads).**

**Google Adsense[Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/)**

**Google Analytics   [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).**

## How long we retain your data

we donot store and retain any user data but the services we use may retain the users data for which we mention the details and links in above section

## Additional information

We never share your information with other organizations. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected  via third-party sites that may be accessed through hyperlinks on this Website. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies.  If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our Website may not work properly in your case. If you have any questions or concerns about this, or any other aspect of your experience on www.fashionuniverse.net send us email at admin@fashionuniverse.net

**Contact us at admin@fashionuniverse.net**

Updated on 24/05/2018
